daichi o fumishimete
Stepping firmly on the ground,
kimi wa mezameteiku
you are awakening.
tenshi no hohoemi de
With the smile of an angel,
tsuredashite!
take me away!
kodoku demo hitori ja nai sa
You are not alone, even in solitude.
umarete kita kotoni kanarazu imi ga aru
There is definitely a reason as to why we are born.
taiyou abite
Bathing in the sun...
sekai wa kimi no kagayaki o materu
The world is awaiting your brilliance!
daichi o fumishimete
Stepping firmly on the ground,
kimi wa mezameteiku
you are awakening.
tenshi no hohoemi de
With the smile of an angel,
tsuredashite! (you can smile!)
take me away! (you can smile!)
“hajimari” wa itsudemo osokunaisa
It is never too late for a new “beginning”
nando demo tachiagare!
No matter what happens, keep getting back up!
Departure × And × Friends
Whale Island
Hunter Vocabulary
Gon
kasanatteta mune no oto
The sound of overlapping hearts.
yusabutte mo kikoenai
They're vibrating, yet I can't hear them.
koboreochita piisu
The scattered pieces.
konna nichijou no yuutsu sae
In spite of how depressing today is,
tameiki mo dezu ni mukanjou na bokura
we show no emotion, not even a sigh.
Life filled with vanity
Colors have faded. Things you desire exists here!
Flee from this colorless world!
tsugihagi no kokoro wa fuantei
Our patched-up hearts are insecure.
arainagasareta shoki shoudou o
Reawaken your primal instincts
yobisamashite hashiridase
and start running.
tsutanai kotoba
A clumsy choice of words.
omou mama ni tsunagu yo ano hi no kodou o
So that we can come together, as I desire,
wasurenai de
don't forget that day.
Oh my lord, it's gone! What shall I do?
Pieces I had have fell apart.
Where do you belong? Where should I aim?
Once you've lost sight it's left to fall apart.