daichi o fumishimete
Stepping firmly on the ground,
kimi wa mezameteiku
you are awakening.
tenshi no hohoemi de
With the smile of an angel,
tsuredashite!
take me away!
kodoku demo hitori ja nai sa
You are not alone, even in solitude.
umarete kita kotoni kanarazu imi ga aru
There is definitely a reason as to why we are born.
taiyou abite
Bathing in the sun...
sekai wa kimi no kagayaki o materu
The world is awaiting your brilliance!
daichi o fumishimete
Stepping firmly on the ground,
kimi wa mezameteiku
you are awakening.
tenshi no hohoemi de
With the smile of an angel,
tsuredashite! (you can smile!)
take me away! (you can smile!)